<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PV Creations – </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on PV Creations</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 15:33:52 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rebrand</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/rebrand/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 08:10:34 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/rebrand/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;A rebrand was long overdue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But first, here&amp;rsquo;s the backstory of the original PV Creations logo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The original logo&lt;span class=&#34;hx-absolute -hx-mt-20&#34; id=&#34;the-original-logo&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#the-original-logo&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I created PV Creations&amp;rsquo; original logo in 2021 on an app called Vectornator (now known as &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linearity.io/curve/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Linearity Curve&lt;/a&gt;). The logo comprises the letters &amp;ldquo;PVC&amp;rdquo; enclosed in a circle. The logo received a few tweaks over the years, but its fundamanetals remained unchanged. I originally intended that the logo was change color over time, but this was quickly abandoned and the original purple gradient stuck. This was later changed to a solid purple envisaged as an &amp;ldquo;in-between&amp;rdquo; of the two.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The original logo was never available in SVG format, not because of some technical limitation, but because 1. I didn&amp;rsquo;t know how to edit SVG files using a text editor (doesn&amp;rsquo;t help that TextEdit sucks) and 2. I never thought I&amp;rsquo;d need one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the end of 2023 I got a &amp;ldquo;new&amp;rdquo; Windows PC. Unfortunately Linearity Curve is only available for the iPad and Mac. I don&amp;rsquo;t have an iPad, and my Mac had become unbearably slow. I never took the opportunity to vectorize it, although I probably should&amp;rsquo;ve.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The new logo&lt;span class=&#34;hx-absolute -hx-mt-20&#34; id=&#34;the-new-logo&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#the-new-logo&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most importantly PV Creations&amp;rsquo; new logo isn&amp;rsquo;t too different from the original, but I made a few changes:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Typeface&lt;/strong&gt;: Agency FB replaces Poppins as the PVC logo&amp;rsquo;s font. A condensed font (at least on Windows), Agency FB takes up more vertical space within the circle, making the logo more visually appealing and – in my opinion, at least – proportional.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;and that&amp;rsquo;s about it. It&amp;rsquo;s already live as the Discord server&amp;rsquo;s icon and will be rolled out to other PVC outlets in due course. Let me know what you think in the Discord server!&lt;/p&gt;
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
